The noble tree house – all natural materials, sturdy construction, aloof from the troubles of the world.
高耸的树屋——全天然材料、坚固的结构、远离尘世的纷扰。
In a more dangerous time in human history, their position above the ground would protect the dweller against environmental difficulties and possible predators.
在人类历史上更危险的时期，它们远离地面，可以保护居住者免受恶劣环境和潜在捕食者的威胁。
As modern construction has improved, these arboreal residences have become less of a practical dwelling and more of a children's novelty - a secret den erected in many a back garden.
随着现代建筑技术的进步，这些树木住宅逐渐不再是实用的住所，而更像是孩子们的新奇事物——许多后花园里搭建的秘密巢穴。
But now, these fun shelters are appealing to adults too and many are booking themselves in for a few nights among the treetops.
但现在，这些有趣的庇护所也吸引了成年人，许多人会预订在树梢间住上几晚。
These tree house hotels can be found from Europe to Australia.
从欧洲到澳大利亚，都能找到这些树屋酒店。
Best of all, they come in a variety of interesting designs!
最棒的是，它们有着各种有趣的设计！
From the traditional 'four walls and a roof' habitation, such as at TreeHouse Point, in Washington, North America, to the more artistic Nothofagus Hotel in Chilean Patagonia, whose twelve-sided walls make it look like a beehive.
从传统的“四面墙加屋顶”的住所，比如北美华盛顿的TreeHouse Point，到智利巴塔哥尼亚更具艺术性的Nothofagus酒店，其十二面墙使其看起来像一个蜂巢。
If that doesn't appeal, how about a tree pod?
如果这还不够吸引人，那树荚状的树屋呢？
The Free Spirit Spheres resort on Vancouver Island in Canada allows guests to stay in one of three yellow spheres, which are suspended from trees.
加拿大温哥华岛的“自由精神球体”度假村允许客人住在三个悬挂在树上的黄色球体中。
The company was founded in 1998 by Tom Chudleigh, who hand built the pods from cedar wood and fibre glass, and then added fixtures and fittings.
该公司由汤姆・查德利（Tom Chudleigh）于1998年创立，他用雪松和玻璃纤维手工建造了这些舱体，然后添加了固定装置和家具。
Not only are they as safe as houses, they're popular!
它们不仅像普通房屋一样安全，而且很受欢迎！
Visitor numbers have probably doubled in the past five years, Mr Chudleigh tells the BBC.
查德利先生告诉BBC，过去五年里，游客数量可能翻了一番。
Digs which are original seem to be a big draw.
独特的住宅似乎很有吸引力。
In Sweden, at the Treehotel, numbers have also risen.
在瑞典的树屋酒店（Treehotel），客人数量也在增加。
"In 2010, we had four rooms and around 1,500 guests a year.
“2010年，我们有四个房间，每年约1500名客人。
Today we have seven rooms and nearly 5,000 guests,"
如今我们有七个房间，近5000名客人，”肯特・林德瓦尔（Kent Lindvall）解释道。
Kent Lindvall explains. Mr Lindvall co-owns the Treehotel with his wife Britta Lindvall.
林德瓦尔先生和妻子布里塔・林德瓦尔（Britta Lindvall）共同经营这家树屋酒店。
Each of the domiciles there was designed by an architect, who was asked to make use of the light and surroundings.
那里的每一间住所都由建筑师设计，他被要求充分利用光线和周围环境。
Their abodes include a mirrored cube, a bird's nest and a UFO.
他们的居所包括镜面立方体、鸟巢和不明飞行物（UFO）造型的树屋。
And how about an office?
那办公室呢？
Microsoft, hoping to give its employees thinking space, has commissioned a three-building structure from Pete Nelson, tree house book author and designer and builder of tree houses.
微软希望为员工提供思考空间，委托树屋书籍作者、树屋设计师和建造者皮特・纳尔逊（Pete Nelson）设计了一个由三座建筑组成的树屋办公区。
"Studies show people can work better in nature. They are more productive," says Mr Nelson.
“研究表明，人们在自然环境中工作效率更高，”纳尔逊先生说。
If you've no head for heights, then maybe a tree house getaway isn't going to be your home away from home.
如果你恐高，那么树屋度假可能不会成为你的“第二故乡”。
But the sense of adventure, the novelty of the setting and the opportunity to return to nature has given an increasing number of tree house-staying adults something to write home about.
但冒险的感觉、环境的新奇感以及回归自然的机会，让越来越多入住树屋的成年人有了值得分享的体验。